you guys it says solve for x no
calculator so step one I'm going to
cross multiply so on the left hand side
I get x minus 2 times X plus 2 and then
5 times 13 is equal to 65. so we can
multiply out the left-hand side x times
x is x squared x times 2 is 2x negative
2 times x is negative 2X and negative 2
times 2 is negative 4. and it's still
equal to 65. this negative 2X and
positive 2x are going to cancel each
other out we're just left with x squared
minus 4 equals 65. so then we can add 4
to both sides these two cancel each
other out which gives us x squared
equals and 65 plus 4 is 69. nice square
root both sides and we get x equals a
plus or minus root 69 nice and that's
the answer to the question how exciting